Greenbaum, Marcia Papers 6091
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Arbitration Documents: 1982 Allyn and Bacon-- New England Telephone. (Box 23)
  - Town of Danvers and Mass. Nurses Assn. RA3-1983 ARB 82, 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Deerfield Plastics Inc. and UE, Local 274 AAA #1130-1564-82 ARB 82, 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Dennison National and OPEU AAA #1130-2330-81 ARB 82, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Edgewood Convalescent CTR, and District 1199 AAA #1130-1598-82 ARB 82, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - WM. Filene Sons Company and U.F.C.W., Local 1445 AAA #1130-0581-82 ARB 82, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - WM. Filene's Sons Co. and UFCW, Local 1445 AAA #1130-1867-82 ARB 82, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - General Tire Co. URW, Local 971 AAA #1130-0458-82 ARB 82, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - City of Gloucester and Gloucester Firefighters, Loc. 762 AAA #1139-1053-82 ARB 82, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Great Northern Paper Co. and Office & Prof. EES., Local 172 FMCS #82K/13215 ARB 82, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - City of Groton, Connecticut and USWA, Local 13280 FMCS #81K/24137 ARB 82, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Harrington & Richardson, Inc. and IUE, Local 262 AAA #1130-1958-82 ARB 82, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Harvard Community Health Plan S.E.I.U., Local 285 AAA #1130-1345-82 ARB 82, 1981-1983 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - ITT Royal Electric Day and IBEW, Local 1196 AAA #1130-2294-81 ARB 82, 1981-1983 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - J.K. Electronics Co. and U.E. Local 274 Discharge AAA #1130-0408-82 ARB 82, 1981-1982 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Town of Kingston and Kingston Firefighters, Local 2337 AAA #1139-1734-82 ARB 82, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Marlboro Hospital and mass. Nurse Assoc. ARB 82 AAA #1139-2471-81, 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - MNA/Marlborough Hospital Interest Arbitration MNA Exhibits, 1981-1982 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Massachusetts Electric Co. and UWUA, Local 446 Gr. 028-81 AAA #1130-0276-82 ARB 82, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Milford Board of Education and AAA #1239-0259-82 ARB 82 Milford Education Association, 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - M.I.T. and S.E.I.U., Local 254 D. AAA #1130-1527-82 ARB 82, 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - New England Telephone and I.B.E.W., Local 2222 AAA #1130-0784-78 ARB 82, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - New England Telephone and I.B.E.W., Local 2222 AAA #1130-0437-77 ARB 82, 1977-1983 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - New Jersey Bell Telephone and IBEW, Local 827 AAA #1330-0111-82 ARB 82, 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 41)
- Arbitration Documents: 1982 New Jersey Bell-- Yale. (Box 24)
  - Notes of Pres John D'Errico (Copies) BIF/USWA #1139-0766-82, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - New Jersey Bell Telephone Co. and I.B.E.W. Local 827 AAA # 1330-0713-82 ARB 82, 1982-1983 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - In the Matter of the Arbitration -between- Local 827 IBEW -and- New Jersey Bell Telephone Company, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - NYS Dept. of Correctional Serv. And NYS/82 81-149-D ARB 82 AFSCME, Council 82, 1981-1982 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - North Adams State College and AFSCME, Council 93, Local 1067 ARB 82 J. Maruco, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Okonite Company and IBEW, Local 1450 AAA #1130-1351-82 ARB 82, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Pratt & Whitney Machine Tool and Unity Lodge Local 405 AAA #1230-0349-82 ARB 82, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - City of Quincy and Quincy Police Betterment Assoc. ARB 82, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Quinnipiac College and Quinnipiac Faculty Federation AAA #1239-0368-82 ARB 82, 1982-1983 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Rathbone Corporation and U.S.W.A. AAA #1130-1303-82 ARB 82, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Rollins Outdoor Advertising and Sheet Metal Workers, Local 194 FMCS #82K/28322 ARB 82, 1979-1983 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Salem News Publishing Company and Newspaper Guild of Salem AAA #1130-1845-82 ARB 82, 1982-1983 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - City of Somerville and International Association of Firefighters, Local 1240 JLMC-81-19-F, 1981-1983 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - City of Somerville and IAFF, Local 1240 JLMC-81-19F Factfinding 82 (Folder 1 of 2), 1974-1982 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - City of Somerville and IAFF, Local 1240 JLMC-81-19F Factfinding 82 (Folder 2 of 2), 1982 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Thermet, Inc. and Teamsters, Local 42 FMCS #82K/26657 ARB 82, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Timex Clock Co. and U.E., Local 205 Gr. 3-82 AAA #1130-0525-82 ARB 82, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Trans World Airlines and Donna Sowell Gr. 1137 ARB 82, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Type & Steel Co. of N.E. and Teamsters, Local 379 ARB 82, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Dept. of the Air Force and AFGE, Local 1285 FMCS #82K/05446 ARB 82, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - DHHS, Social Security Admin. And AFGE, Local 3760 FMCS #82K/10970 ARB 82, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - USM Bailey and UAW, Local 1913 AAA #1130-0986-82 ARB 82, 1982-1983 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - U.S. Customs Service and 82 FSIP 49 ARB 82 N.T.E.U., 1982-1983 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - S.D. Warren Co. and U.P.I.U, Local 1069 AAA #1130-0831-82 ARB 82, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - WCVB-TB Channel 5 and AFTRA Harrington Grievance ARB 82 Direct, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Western Electric and C.W.A., Local 1365 Arb 82, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Town of Westwood and AAA #1139-0021-82 Arb 82 Prof. Police Officers Assn., 1981-1983 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Whyn Stations Corp and ArB 82 AAA #1130-0343-82 Nabet Gr. G82-3, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Woonsocket School Committee and Woonsocket Teachers Guild AAA #1139-2525-81 ARB 82, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Yale University and F.U.E., Local 35 Arb 82, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 30)
- Arbitration Documents: 1983 Anaconda-- Conn. Light. (Box 25)
  - Anaconda Industries and U.S.W.A., Local 6445 AAA #1230-0084-83 ARB 83, 1982-1983 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Associated Grocers and Teamsters Local 340 FMCS #83K/22315 ARB 83, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Bailey Corp. and UAW, Local 1913 AAA #1130-0390-83 ARB 83, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - In the Matter for Arbitration Between United Auto Workers 1913 -and- Bailey Corporation Case No. 1130-0390-83, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Bancroft & Martin, Inc. and Truck Drivers, Local 340 FMCS #83K/03665 ARB 83, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Bates Fabrics Inc and A.G.T.W.U. FMCS 83K/19158 ARB 83, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - BIW Cable System, Inc. and IAMAW, Lodge 264 ARB 83, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - BD. Regents Framingham St. Coll. And AFSCME, C. 93, #1067 ARB 83 Class Action, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - BD. Of Regents-Mass. And MTA Coll. Of Art ARB 83, 1982-1984 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - BD. Of Regents Mass. Maritime and ARB 83 MTA/APA, 1981-1984 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - BD. Of Regents, No.Adams S.C. and Mass. Teachers Assn. ARB 83, 1981-1983 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - BD. Regents Salem State College and AFSCME Council 93, #1067 ARB 83 Carpenter Shop, 1983-1985 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - BD. Of Regents Westfield St. Col. And MTA Gr. ARB 83, 1982-1984 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Boise Cascade and U.P.I.U., Local 900 AAA#1130-0068-83 ARB 83, 1982-1983 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Bristol Board of Education and Bristol Federation of Teachers AAA #1239-0398-82 ARB 83, 1982-1983 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - City of Buffalo and Buffalo Police Benev. Assn. A81-320 ARB 83, 1982-1983 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Capital Cities Communications and AFTRA Discharge AAA #1230-0424-82 ARB 83 (Folder 1 of 2), 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Capital Cities Communications and AFTRA Discharge AAA #1230-0424-82 ARB 83 (Folder 2 of 2), 1981-1983 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Cesco Brass, LTD. And UAW Local 1251 AAA # 1230-0276-83 RB 83, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Chandler Evans Inc. and UAW, Unity Lodge Local 405 AAA #1230-0466-82 ARB 83, 1982-1983 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Chandler Evans Inc. and UAW, Local 405 AAA #1230-0219-83 ARB 83, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Clinical Assays and OCAWIU, Local 8-366 FMCS #83K/12521 ARB 83, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - City of Cohoes ARB 83, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Conn. Light & Power and IBEW, Locals 420 & 457 AAA #1230-0152-83 (Folder 1 of 2), 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Conn. Light & Power and IBEW, Locals 420 & 457 AAA #1230-0152-83 (Folder 2 of 2), 1976-1983 (Box 25, Folder 25)
- Arbitration Documents: 1983 Conn. UN. Labor-- ODonnell. (Box 26)
  - Connecticut Light & Power Company and Local 420, IBEW (Folder 1 of 2), 1983 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Connecticut Light & Power Company and Local 420, IBEW (Folder 2 of 2), 1983 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Connecticut Light & Power Company -and- Local 420 and 457, I.B.E.W., 1983 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - IBEW, Local 420 and Local 457 -and- Connecticut Light & Power Company RE: Non-Emergency Work, 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Conn. Un. Labor Community Service and IAMAW District 91 AAA #1230-0298-83 ARB 83, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - University of Connecticut and Prof. Employees Assoc. AAA #1239-0061-83 ARB 83, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Emery Worldwide and Teamsters Local 25 FMCS #83K/26001 ARB 83, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Glastonbury Board of Education and Glastonbury Ed. Sec. Assn. AAA #1239-0156-83 ARB 83, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - The Gorton Group and UFCW, Local 15 ARB 83, 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Jewish Memorial Hospital and District 1199 AAA #1130-2415-82 ARB 83, 1980-1983 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Jewish Memorial Hospital and Dist. 11-00 - AAA #1130-2415-82 ARB 83, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Jewish Memorial Hospital and District 1199 AAA #1130-2415-82 ARB 83, 1980-1983 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Jewish Memorial Hospital and Dist. 1199 AAA #1130-2415-82 83, 1982-1984 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Logan Hilton and H.R.I.E. & B.U., Local 26 AAA #1130-1209-83 ARB 83, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - City of Lynn and I.A.F.F., Local 739 AAA #1139-2040-82 ARB 83, 1982-1984 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - MBTA and MBTA Starters & Inspectors AAA #1139-1193-83 ARB 83, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority -and- Starters ad Inspectors Union, Local 600- First Day, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    Grievance of Lawrence LeBeau re suspension without just cause
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority -and- Starters and Inspectors Union, Local 600, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    Re: Grievance of Lawrence LeBeau.
  - Mass. Turnpike Authority and Teamsters. Local 127 R. Tourville, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Milford Mental Health Clinic and AFSCME, Local 1303 AAA #1230-0270-83, 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - National Sea Products and Boilermakers, Local 142 AAA #1130-2304-82 ARB 83, 1982-1983 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - NYS Dept. of Correctional Serv. And AFSCME Council 82 ARB 83 82-173-D C. Calhoun, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Nonotuck Manufacturing Co. and Nonotuck EES. Association AAA #1991-83 ARB 83, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - of North Adams and North Adams Police Assn. RA-6-1983 ARB 83, 1982-1983 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - O'Donnell-Usen Fisheries Corp. and UFCW, Local 15 ARB 83, 1982-1984 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Arbitration Documents: 1983 Providence-- Western Electric. (Box 27)
  - The Providence Journal Bulletin and AGAIU, Local 39-P AAA #130-1026-83 ARB 83 (Folder 1 of 2), 1984 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - The Providence Journal Bulletin and GAIU, Local 39-P AAA #130-1026-83 ARB 83 (Folder 1 of 2), 1984 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Photoengravers Negotiations GAIU Local 39-P Meetings 1-12, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - In the Matter of Arbitration Between: Graphics Arts International Union Local 39-P -and- The Providence Journal Bulletin No. 1130-1026-83, 1983-1984 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Pullman-Higgins and Plumbers #131 AAA #1130-0072-83 ARB 83, 1982-1983 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Ren Electronics and IUE, Local 208 Seniority AAA #1130-1765-83 ARB 83, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Safety Elec. Equipment Corp. and ARB 83 UE, Local 296 Discharge, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Seymour Board of Education and Seymour Education Assn. AAA #1230-0113-83 ARB 83, 1983-1984 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Sheaffer Eaton and U.P.I.U., Local 882 AAA #1130-2050-82 ARB 83, 1980-1983 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Stanley Works and IAM, Lodge 1433, 1982-1983 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Stride Rite Corp. and UFCW, Local 1445 FMCS #83K/22616 ARB 83, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Terry Corp. and IUE, Local 289 Gr. 22-82 FMCS #83K/15349 ARB 83, 1983-1984 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - In the Matter of: Local No. 289, International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, A.F.L.-C.I.O and The Terry Corporation of Connecticut Grievance Nos. 47-83 and 48-83, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Torrington Company and AAA 12 30 0256 83 ARB 83 and UAW Local 1645, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - U.S. Repeating Arms Co. and IAMAW Victor Lodge 609 FMCS #83K/ 13069 ARB 83, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - West Point Pepperell Inc. and FMCS #83K/18783 AC&TWU, Local 305T Gr. #15, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Western Electric Co. and CWA, Local 1365 #WEM-82-135 (477) FMCS #82K/23452 ARB 83 (Folder 1 of 2), 1984-1985 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Western Electric Co. and CWA, Local 1365 #WEM-82-135 (477) FMCS #82K/23452 ARB 83 (Folder 2 of 2), 1983-1984 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - In the Matter of Arbitration of: Western Electric and CWA, Local 1365, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - No. 82K/23452 In the Matter of Arbitration of Western Electric (AT&T Technologies) and CWA, Local 1365, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- Arbitration Documents: 1983 Western Electric-- 1984 Henry Heywood Memorial Hospital. (Box 28)
  - Western Union Telegraph Co. and United Telegraph Workers Case #44-83 ARB 83, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Woonsocket School Committee and Woonsocket Teachers Guild AAA #1139-0359-83 ARB 83 (Folder 1 of 2), 1983-1984 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Woonsocket School Committee and Woonsocket Teachers Guild AAA #1139-0359-83 ARB 83 (Folder 2 of 2), 1976-1983 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Western Electric Co. and CWA Local 1366 #WEM-82-173 (Folder 1 of 2), 1975-1984 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Western Electric Co. and CWA Local 1366 #WEM-82-173 (Folder 2 of 2), 1983-1984 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Boston Edison Co. and UWUA, Local 387 AAA# 1139-2316-83 ARB 83, 1983-1984 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Arbitration between Boston Edison Company -and- Local 387, Utility Workers of America AFL-CIO, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Boston Edison Company -and- Local 387, Utility Workers Union of America AFL-CIO, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Brattleboro Memorial Hospital and Brattleboro Fedn. Of Nurses 5064 AAA #1130-2434-83 ARB 84, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Chandler Evans Inc. and AAA #1230-0406-83 ARB 84 UAW, Local 404 J. Jarrow, 1983-1984 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Chandler Evans Inc. and AAA #1230-0345-83 ARB 83 UAW, Local 405, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Colonnade Hotel and AAA #1130-2374-83 ARB 84 HRIE & BU, Local 26 R. Crisostomo, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - BD. Of Trustees Conn. St. Tech. Coll. Norwalk State Technology College and AAA #1230-0458-83 ARB 84 CSFT, Local 1942, 1983- 1984 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - University of Connecticut and AAA #1230-0163-84 Med/FF U.C.P.E.A., 1984-1985 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Copley Plaza Hotel and AAA #1130-2288-83 ARB 84 H.R.I.E. & B.U. Local 26 J.Diaz, 1980-1983 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - I.B.E.W., Local 1973 -and- Craig System Corporation GR: Dental Plan, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Data Documents / Pitney Bowes and AAA #1230-0417-83 ARB 84 Printing & Comm. Wkrs. Local 650, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Enterprise Publishing Co. and AAA #1330-0274-84 ARB84 Brockton Typo. Union Local 24, 1984-1985 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Funfair Bearing and IAM Gr. 84-001 ARB 84, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Harco Labs, Inc. ARB 84 UE, Local 299, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Framingham Union Hospital and AAA #1130-1548-84 ARB 84 S.E.I.U. Local 285 Termination, 1984-1985 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Harco Labs, Inc. and ARB 84 UE, Local 299, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Harrington & Richardson Inc. And AAA #1130-2456-83 ARB 84 I.U.E., Local 262, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Harrington & Richardson Inc. and AAA #1130-2130-83 ARB 84 IUE, Local 262, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Town of Hartford, Vermont and MED 1984 I.A.F.F. Local 2905 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Henry Heywood Memorial Hospital and AAA #1139-2264-83 ARB 84 S.E.I.U., Local 285, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 26)
- Arbitration Documents: 1984 Hillsborough City-- Market Forge. (Box 29)
  - Hillsborough City Sheriff Dept. and AAA #1139-1889-83 ARB 84 AFSCME Council 68, Local 2715, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - HNS Management Co., Inc. and AAA #1230-269-84 ARB 84 ATU, Local 425 Discharge (Folder 1 of 2), 1984-1985 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - HNS Management Co., Inc. and AAA #1230-269-84 ARB 84 ATU, Local 425 Discharge (Folder 2 of 2), 1980-1983 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Institute of Living and AAA #1230-0097-84 ARB 84 District 1199, NEHC, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union Local 425 and HNS Management Company, Inc., Discharge Case No. 12 30 269 84, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union Local 425 and HNS Management Company, Inc., Discharge, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - James River-OTIS Inc. and FMCS #84K/19412 ARB 84 UPIU, Local 11, 1980-1985 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - U.P.I.U., Local #449 and Keyes Fibre, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Lincoln, R.I. School Committee and AAA #1139-0047-84 ARB 84 Lincoln Teaches Association (Folder 1 of 2), 1983-1984 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Lincoln, R.I. School Committee and AAA #1139-0047-84 ARB 84 Lincoln Teaches Association (Folder 2 of 2), 1983-1984 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Minuteman Regl. Voc. Tech. School D and AAA #1139-1796-83 ARB 84 Minuteman Regl. Faculty Fedn #3191, 1982-1984 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - American Arbitration Assoc. Market Forge Company and United Steelworkers of America AFL-CIO (Folder 1 of 2), 1978-1982 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - American Arbitration Assoc. Market Forge Company and United Steelworkers of America AFL-CIO (Folder 2 of 2), 1982-1984 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - American Arbitration Association United Steelworkers of America, AFL-CIO and Market Forge Company (folder 1 of 2), 1983 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    Grievance of Stephen Legere (AAA. Case No. 1130-0229-84)
  - American Arbitration Association United Steelworkers of America, AFL-CIO and Market Forge Company (folder 2 of 2), 1984-1985 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Massachusetts Sportservice Inc. and AAA #1139-0679-84 ARB 84 UFSW Local 1445, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Lincoln, 1983-1984 (Box 29, Folder 17)
- Arbitration Documents: 1984 Narragansett-- U.S. Postal Service. (Box 30)
  - Narragansett Electric Co. Arb 84 and BUWNE. Local 310 G. Malloy, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - New England Telephone and Mediation 1984 Ms. Ann New England Telephone and Mediation 1984 Ms. Ann Morley, 1976-1984 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Northeast Offset, Inc. and AAA #2230-2572-84 ARB 84 Lowell PrintG. & Graph. Local 109, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - City of Quincy and AAA #1139-1399-84 ARB 84 Quincy Police Betterment Assn., 1983-1985 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Quincy City Hospital and AAA #1139-0474-84 ARB 84 S.E.I.U. Local l285, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Page Wilson Corp. And AAA #1230-0182-84 ARB 84 USWA, Local 4818 #83-17, 32,35, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Page Wilson Corp. and AAA #1230-0183-84 ARB 84 USWA Local 4818 Gr. 83-18, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Parsons Paper and AAA #1130-0694-84 ARB 84 U.P.I.U Local 226 Discharge, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Pratt & Whitney and AAA #1230-0444-83 ARB 84 U.A.W. Local 405, 1983-1984 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Putnam Herzl Finishing and AAA #1230-0004-84 ARB 84 SO. N. E. Joint Board, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - State of Rhode Island and AAA #1139-0457-84 ARB 84 AFSCME, Council 94 (Transp.), 1981-1984 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - State of Rhode Island and AAA #1139-0457-84 ARB 84 AFSCME, C. 94, Locals 1350 MHRH, 1983-1985 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - State of Rhode Island and AAA #1139-0375-84 ARB 84 NAGE Local 79, 1983-1985 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Schaffer Marine Inc. and Teamsters, Local 59, 1981-1983 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Sears Roebuck & Co. and ARB 84 Discharge Teamsters, Local 25, 1981-1985 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Sheaffer Eaton and AAA #1130-0691-84 ARB 84 U.P.I.U. # 882 38-83, 90-83, 100-83, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - City of Springfield and AAA #1139-0311-84 ARB 84 NAGE, Local RL-289, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - St. Joseph Hospital and AAA #1139-0316-84 ARB 84 St. Joseph FEDN. Of Nurses, 1981-1984 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Strathmore Paper and AAA #1130-2275-83 ARB 84 UPIU #197 Gr. 2-13 & 2-30, 1982-1986 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Trans World Airlines and Gr. #11670 ARB 84, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Triangle Pacific Co. and AAA #1130-2443-83 ARB 84 United Furniture Workers, 1983-1984 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - U.S. Postal Service ARB. 84 and N1C-1A-D 27078 A.P.W.U., 1983-1984 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - U.S. Postal Service and N1C-1A-D 23772; 24914 ARB 84 A.P.W.U. V. Byrd, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - U.S. Postal Service and N1C-1M-D 22027 A.P.W.U. ARB 84, 1984-1985 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - U.S. Postal Service and N1C-1A-D 19323 APWU ARB 84, 1984-1985 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - U.S. Postal Service and N1C-1A-D 15638 APWU ARB 84, 1984-1985 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - U.S. Postal Service and N1C-1A-D 18951 APWU ARB 84, 1983-1984 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - U.S. Postal Service and N1C-1A-D 16494 ARB 84 APWU L. Gentile, 1981-1984 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - U.S. Postal Service and N1C-1M-D ARB 84 A.P.W.U. 21032, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - U.S. Postal Service and N1C-1M-D 31860 ARB 84 A.P.W.U. D. Milstein, 1984-1985 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - U.S. Postal Service and N1C-1A-D 11629 Arb 84 APWU B. O'Hare, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 31)
- Arbitration Documents: 1984 U.S. Postal Service-- 1985 Corando. (Box 31)
  - U.S. Postal Service and N1C-1A-D 17265 ARB 84 APWU N. Rivera, 1982-1985 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - U.S. Postal Service ARB 84 and N1C-1A-D 25896 J. Rosner A.P.W.U., 1984 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Postal Service and N1C-1E-D 19622 ARB 84 APWU B. Smith, 1983-1984 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - U.S. Postal Service and N1C-1A-D 16501 APWU R. Spikener, 1983-1985 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - U.S. Postal Service ARB 84 and #N1N-1E-D 34592; 34591 N.A.L.C. J. Ouellette, 1984-1985 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - U.S. Postal Service and N1N-1A-D 16824 N.A.L.C. ARB 84, 1983-1984 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - U.S. Postal Service and N1N-1A-D 19658 N.A.L.C. ARB 84, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - U.S. Postal Service and N1M-1M-D 32960 ARB 84 N.A.M.H. L. Cruz, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - U.S. Postal Service and N1M-1M-D 22944 ARB 84 N.A.M.H. D. Guenzel, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Unheard Postal Service Cases 1984 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - WBZ Radio and AAA #1130-0153-84 ARB 84 IBEW, Local 1228 J.DiTroia, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Town of Westerly and AAA #1139-0374-84 ARB 84 Frat. Order Police Lodge #10, 1984-1985 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Weyerhauser Co. and AAA #1130-2420-83 ARB 84 UPIU #669, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Wrighton Typographers and ARB 84 Boston Typo. Union Local 13 (Folder 1 of 2), 1985 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Wrighton Typographers and ARB 84 Boston Typo. Union Local 13 (Folder 2 of 2), 1982-1985 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Wyman-Gordon Co. and W-3-82-34 ARB 84 USWA, Direct One, 1983-1984 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Wyman-Gordon Co. and W-3-83-2 ARB 84 USWA, District One, 1983-1984 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Yale University and ARB 84 Gr. F.U.E. Local 35 #6745, 1983-1985 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Yale University and ARB 84 F.U.E., Local 35, 1982-1984 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Yale University and ARB 84 Gr. #1980-6216 F.U.E. Local 35, 1982-1986 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - American Overseas Marine Corp. and Seafarers Intl. Union, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - American Tools & Machine Co. and FMCS #85K/28682 ARB 85 IAMAW, Local 1376 Discharge, 1984-1985 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Town of Amesbury and JLMC-84-46P Factfinding 85 Amesbury Police Association, 1981-1985 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Bacon Felt Co. and ARB 85 U.E., Local 226, 1985-1986 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Bechtel Constructors Corp. and FMCS #85K/09582 ARB 85 Boilermakers Local 29, 1978-1986 (Box 31, Folder 25)